Guide to the Franco Modigliani papers, 1936-2005 and undated, bulk 1970s-2003 RL.00905
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Professional Service Series, 1961-2002 and undated, 16 boxes
  - International Economics Association Subseries, 1976-1983 and undated
    Contains minutes of the executive committee of the International Economics Association (IEA), correspondence; programs of meetings which Modigliani organized or in which he participated; drafts of papers presented; and financial matters and patron contributions to the association. The IEA is committed to promoting personal contacts and to facilitating discussions and free exchange among different economists around the world. The meetings represented in this subseries covered relevant economic and social problems of the time. Arranged in chronological order by the conference date, then alphabetical by subject or last name. The city in which the conference was located is also listed.
    - 1976-1978, Executive committee meetings and conference programs (Box PS9)
    - 1976-1984, Various correspondence, reports, executive meetings, and a paper about the I.E.A. (Box PS9)
    - 1977-1980, Correspondence with Austin Robinson (Box PS9)
    - 1977-1980, New memberships (Box PS9)
    - 1977-1981, Financial matters
      - Finance drive (Box PS9)
      - I.E.A. and Ford Foundation (Box PS9)
      - Patron contributors (Box PS9)
      - Subscriptions (Box PS9)
    - 1977, Tokyo
      - Correspondence, executive committee meetings and program (1976-1977) (Box PS9)
      - Plenary sessions (papers) (Box PS9)
    - 1978 June, Poland (1977-1978) (Box PS9)
    - 1978 Aug., Strasbourg (1978), 2 folders (Box PS9)
    - circa 1979, Workshop in South Asia (undated) (Box PS9)
    - 1979 June, Kiel (1979-1980 and undated), folders 1-3 of 6 (Box PS9)
    - 1979 June, Kiel (1979-1980 and undated), folders 4-6 of 6 (Box PS10)
    - 1979 June, Moscow (1978) (Box PS10)
    - 1979 Aug., London, executive committee meeting (1978-1980) (Box PS10)
    - 1980-1982, Correspondence with Victor Uquidi (Box PS10)
    - 1980 Mar., India (1978-1980) (Box PS10)
    - 1980 June, Bergamo
      - Author's abstracts (1980) (Box PS10)
      - Correspondences with discussants (1980) (Box PS10)
      - Correspondences with presenters (1979-1981) (Box PS10)
      - Correspondences with Russian economists (1979-1980) (Box PS10)
      - Finances (1979-1980) (Box PS10)
      - Local organizing committee (1977-1980) (Box PS10)
      - Luc Fauvel and Mary Crook (1977-1980) (Box PS10)
      - Papers
        - R. Bentzel, L. Berg (Box PS10)
        - R. Goldsmith, 2 folders (Box PS10)
        - M. Nasilowksi (Box PS10)
        - J. Pickersgill (Box PS10)
    - 1980 June, Bergamo (Box PS11)
      - Papers
        - N. Rossi, E. Tarantelli, C. Tresoldi (Box PS11)
        - M. Shinohara (Box PS11)
        - D. Strauss-Kahn (Box PS11)
      - Possible invitees and possible papers (Box PS11)
      - Program committee (1979-1980) (Box PS11)
      - Program committee, old information (1976-1979) (Box PS11)
      - Programs, list of participants, reports and notes (1978-1980 and undated) (Box PS11)
      - Publishing conference volume and papers (1980-1982) (Box PS11)
    - 1980 Aug., Mexico (1977-1980), 3 folders (Box PS11)
    - 1981 Sept., Athens (1980-1981) (Box PS11)
    - 1981 Oct., Buenos Aires (1979-1981) (Box PS11)
    - 1982 May, Ottowa (1978-1981) (Box PS11)
    - 1982 Aug., Sweden (1981 and undated) (Box PS12)
    - 1982 Sept., Florence (Box PS12)
    - 1982 Oct., Tokyo (Box PS12)
    - 1982 Dec., New York (1980-1982) (Box PS12)
    - 1983, Nominating committee (1982-1983), 2 folders (Box PS12)
    - 1983 July, Addis Ababa (Box PS12)
    - 1983 Sept., Spain, executive committee meeting (Box PS12)
  - Other Professional Service Subseries, 1963-2002 and undated
    Folders contain correspondence, notebooks, agendas, drafts of papers, notes, minutes, reports, and printed materials related to Modigliani's involvement in non-academic activities. Arranged in alphabetical order by folder title.
    - 401 (K) Credit Card, 1995-2000 (Box PS13)
    - California Federal Bank, 1998, 2 folders (Box PS13)
    - Dibner Institute for the History of Science and Technology, M.I.T., 1985-1999 (Box PS13)
    - E. F. Hutton and Company Inc.
      - Bills, 1979-1980 (Box PS13)
      - Boston presentation, 1979 July (Box PS13)
      - Correspondence, 1979 (Box PS13)
      - New York presentation, 1979 Nov., 2 folders (Box PS13)
      - New York presentation, 1980 July (Box PS13)
      - Peter Smith, market model, 1979 (Box PS13)
    - Econometric model for Quebec, Singh committee, undated (Box PS13)
    - Fininvest, 1991-1993, 3 folders (Box PS13)
    - Fininvest, Promostudio, 1992 (Box PS13)
    - Investment Company Institute, 1970-1973, folder 1 of 3 (Box PS13)
    - Investment Company Institute, 1970-1973, folders 2-3 of 3 (Box PS14)
    - Istituto CIRM, 1997 Aug. 5 (Box PS14)
    - Jerome Levy Economics Institute of Bard College, 1985-2002 (Box PS14)
    - National Academy of Sciences
      - Finance committee meeting, 1974 Dec. 10 (Box PS14)
      - Finance committee meeting, 1975 (Box PS14)
      - Finance committee meeting, 1975 Mar. 24 (Box PS14)
      - General, 1974-1976, 3 folders (Box PS14)
    - New America High Income Fund
      - General, 1997-2000 (Box PS14)
      - Printed material, 1988 (Box PS14)
      - Shares info, 1988 (Box PS15)
    - Treasury Consultants meeting, circa 1963-1971 Feb. 12 and undated, folders 1-16 of 22 (Box PS15)
    - Treasury Consultants meeting, circa 1963-1971 Feb. 12 and undated, folders 17-22 of 22 (Box PS16)
    - Shadow Financial Regulatory Committee
      - General, 1992-1998 and undated (Box PS16)
      - Notebook, 1992-1997, 3 folders (Box PS16)
- Teaching Materials Series, 1940-2003 and undated, 10 boxes
  Divided into Modigliani as Student Subseries and Modigliani as Teacher Subseries.
  - Modigliani as Student Subseries, 1940-1949 and undated
    - Book review notebook, undated (Box T1)
    - Jacob Marschak's course, 1940-1949 (Box T1)
    - Monetary theory notes, undated (Box T1)
    - Statistics course, 1943-1944 (Box T1)
    - Various class notes, 1940s (Box T1)
  - Modigliani as Teacher Subseries, 1952-2003 and undated
    - Advanced Economics, 1952-1960, 2 folders (Box T1)
    - Capital Markets, 1960-1995, folders 1-3 of 62 (Box T1)
    - Capital Markets, 1960-1995, folders 4-17 of 62 (Box T2)
    - Capital Markets, 1960-1995, folders 18-33 of 62 (Box T3)
    - Capital Markets, 1960-1995, folders 34-45 of 62 (Box T4)
    - Capital Markets, 1960-1995, folders 46-58 of 62 (Box T5)
    - Capital Markets, 1960-1995, folders 59-62 of 62 (Box T6)
    - Dean's reports, 1963-1995, 2 folders (Box T6)
    - Dissertation, Christopher Knowles, 1990 June-1992 (Box T6)
    - Economic Fluctation and Growth, 1961 (Box T6)
    - Economics, 1956-1961, 2 folders (Box T6)
    - Faculty meetings, 1962-1963 (Box T6)
    - Finance Seminar, 15.954, 1969 Fall (Box T6)
    - Finance Seminar, 15.441, 1971 Fall-1976 Spring, 6 folders (Box T6)
    - Financial Management, 1962-1965 Fall, 5 folders (Box T6)
    - Italian Economy study group, 1974 (Box T7)
    - Lecture in Frankfurt, 1992-2002 (Box T7)
    - Lectures on stabilization policy, 1981 (Box T7)
    - Macroeconomics, circa 1969-1982 Fall, 4 folders (Box T7)
    - Monetary Economics, 14.462, 1963 Spring-1982 Spring, folders 1-8 of 20 (Box T7)
    - Monetary Economics, 14.462, 1963 Spring-1982 Spring, folders 9-20 of 20 (Box T8)
    - Monetary Theory
      - Notes on advanced Monetary Theory III, 1953-1960 (Box T8)
      - Preliminary notes, 1955-1956, 3 folders (Box T8)
      - Lecture notes, 1955-1956, 2 folders (Box T8)
      - 1960-1967 Spring (Box T9)
    - Monetary Workshop, 1973 Fall (Box T9)
    - Money reading course, 1969 Spring (Box T9)
    - Montpellier lecture, undated (Box T9)
    - Notes
      - Economics of barter systems, undated (Box T9)
      - Effect of interest rate on unemployment, undated (Box T9)
      - Endogenous money, undated (Box T9)
      - Linear programming, undated (Box T9)
      - Monetary mechanism, 1980 (Box T9)
      - Some general principles on the effect of the national debt, 1964 (Box T9)
    - Personnel committee, 1962 (Box T9)
    - Phillips seminar, 1963 (Box T9)
    - Raiffa seminar, 1962 (Box T9)
    - Theses
      - Proposals, 1963-1992, 2 folders (Box T9)
      - Hoornweg, Roberto, 1989-1990 (Box T9)
      - Simon Pietro Felice, 1992 (Box T9)
      - Ivanov, Svilen, 1993 (Box T9)
    - Topics in Finance and Economics, 1996 Spring-2003 Spring, folders 1 of 10 (Box T9)
    - Topics in Finance and Economics, 1996 Spring-2003 Spring, folders 2-10 of 10 (Box T10)
    - Various class notes, 1959-1980s and undated, 3 folders (Box T10)
- Personal Files Series, 1938-2005 and undated, 1 box
  Files contain various documents concerning Modigliani's education, his emigration from Italy in 1939, and other personal history. Includes a DVD of the memorial held at MIT shortly following his death in 2003. Honorary degrees and diplomas are included in this series and in the Oversize Materials. A number of files contain biographical information, including a curriculum vitae, personal reflections, and articles by colleagues honoring Modigliani. Arranged in chronological order.
  - 1938, Sorbonne, French visa application (Box P1)
  - 1941, Proof of Juris Doctorate (Box P1)
  - 1960, American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box P1)
  - 1960-1997, Diplomas and degrees, 4 folders; 34 items (Box P1)
  - 1966-2004, Microfilms (Box P1)
    Archival-quality microfilms produced in 2004 from family scrapbooks containing clippings and other memorabilia related to Modigliani's career.
  - 1967 May 5, University of Chicago Honorary Degree (Box P1)
  - 1967, University of Chicago honorary degree (Box P1)
  - 1974 June, Drèze, Jacques speech in honor of Modigliani (Box P1)
  - 1982, Copy of birth certificate (Box P1)
  - 1985 Mar., One paragraph biography and correspondence (Box P1)
  - 1985 Aug.-1986, May Citation for James R. Killian, Jr. Faculty Achievement Award of M.I.T. (Box P1)
  - 1985 Oct. 16, Confindustria, Rassegna Stampa, newspaper clippings related to Nobel Prize (Box P1)
  - 1985 and undated, Biographies and speeches related to Nobel Prize (Box P1)
  - 1986, Ruminations on my professional life (Box P1)
  - 1986-2004 and undated, Biographical materials (Box P1)
  - 1991 Apr. 27, Intervento del Professor Mario Monti, Premio Internazionale Stivale d'Oro (Box P1)
  - 1991 Apr.-May, Visas and vital statistics (Box P1)
  - 1992 May 26, Addison-Wesley interview (Box P1)
  - circa 1986, 1996, Biographical sketches (Box P1)
  - 1995, Remarks by Ciampi, establishment of Cattedra Modigliani, Rome (Box P1)
  - circa 2003, Curriculum Vitae (Box P1)
  - 2003 Dec. 7, Memorial for Modigliani at MIT (DVD) (Box P1)
  - 2003, English language obituaries and tributes (Box P1)
  - 2003, Italian language obituaries and tributes (Box P1)
  - 2003, Obituaries, 2 folders (Box P1)
  - 2005 Feb., Accademia dei Lincei conference in memory of Modigliani (Box P1)
  - 2005, The Influence of Jacob Marschak, Adolph Lowe, and Hans Neisser on the Formation of Franco Modigliani's work, by Harald Hagemann (includes two letters by Jacob Marschak) (Box P1)
  - Undated, Autobiography (Box P1)
  - Undated, Biography (Box P1)
  - Undated, Biography in French (Box P1)
- Engagements Series, 1963-2003 and undated, 16 boxes
  Divided into the Commitments and Calendars Subseries. Commitments files include routine schedules, correspondence, and itineraries. Some folders contain notes and writings related to the engagement, particularly for conferences. Both subseries arranged in chronological order.
  - Commitments Subseries, 1963-2003 and undated
    - 1963 (Box E1)
      - Dec. 27-29, Econometric Society meeting (Box E1)
    - 1971
      - June 7-11, 21st annual forum on finance, 5 folders (Box E1)
    - 1974
      - Mar. 21-22, Rational expectations conference (Box E1)
    - 1975
      - Aug., Helsinki conference
        - Central Banks (Box E1)
        - Correspondence and photo (Box E1)
        - Discussants (Box E1)
        - General (Box E1)
    - 1975 (Box E2)
      - Aug., Helsinki conference
        - Monetary mechanism in different countries (Box E2)
        - Papers, 4 folders (Box E2)
        - Participants (Box E2)
        - Receipts (Box E2)
        - Travel (Box E2)
    - 1976
      - June, AEA Russian conference (Box E2)
      - Oct., Athens conference
        - Central Banks (Box E2)
        - Discussants (Box E2)
        - General (Box E2)
        - Papers (Box E2)
        - Participants (Box E2)
        - Receipts (Box E2)
        - Supporting materials (Box E2)
    - 1976 (Box E3)
      - Sept., Austria conference
        - Baden hotel (Box E3)
        - Central Banks (Box E3)
        - Comments (Box E3)
        - Discussants (Box E3)
        - Final papers (Box E3)
        - General (Box E3)
        - Kapfer (Box E3)
        - Papers (Box E3)
        - Participants (Box E3)
        - Program (Box E3)
        - Sponsoring committee (Box E3)
      - Dec. 8-9, Conference on income and wealth, Williamsburg (Box E3)
    - 1977-1978, Financial Receipts (Box E3)
    - 1979
      - June, Kiel conference, Germany
        - Authors (Box E3)
        - Central Banks (Box E3)
        - Discussants (Box E3)
        - Expenses (Box E3)
        - Giersch (Box E3)
        - Invitees (Box E3)
        - Miscellaneous (Box E3)
        - Program (Box E3)
        - Sponsoring committee (Box E3)
        - Weltwirtschaftliches archiv (Box E3)
    - 1979-1985 and undated, Financial Receipts (Box E4)
    - 1982
      - Oct. 23-24, Banco di Roma
        - Conference handouts (Box E4)
        - Conference materials (Box E4)
        - Conference pack (Box E4)
        - Correspondence (Box E4)
        - Franco's copies, 2 folders (Box E4)
        - General, 2 folders (Box E4)
        - List of participants (Box E4)
        - Program (Box E4)
        - Publication (Box E4)
    - 1983
      - Aug. 28, Gunnar Eliasson conference (Box E4)
    - 1984 (Box E5)
      - Mar. 29, Hinterhuber Bohn-Bawerk lecture (Box E5)
      - Sept., Genova (Box E5)
      - Oct. 6, Johns Hopkins Bologna Center (Box E5)
      - Oct. 11-12, INA (Rome) (Box E5)
    - 1984-1993
      - Itineraries (Box E5)
    - 1985
      - Mar. 27-28, University of Illinois (Box E5)
      - Apr. 25, Suffolk University (Box E5)
      - June-Nov., Commitments (Box E5)
      - July, Summer session (Box E5)
      - Sept. 19-21, Martha's Vineyard (Box E5)
      - Nov., Argentina (Box E5)
    - 1986
      - Jan. 10, Committee for Responsible Federal Budget (Box E5)
      - Feb. 6, McNeal and Lehrer (Box E5)
      - Feb. 11, Worcester County Bank (Box E5)
      - June 23-24, Retreat (Box E5)
      - June, Paris, Stockholm, Brussels (Box E5)
      - Aug. 12-16, Credit Suisse (Box E5)
      - Sept. 28, Ford Hall forum (Box E5)
      - Sept., Europe (Box E5)
      - Oct. 1, Court (Box E5)
      - Oct. 9-12, Venice (Box E5)
      - Oct. 20, Northeastern University (Box E5)
      - Oct., Brazil (Box E5)
      - Nov. 17, Council on Foreign Relations and Carnegie (Box E5)
      - Dec. 9-13, Helsinki (Box E5)
      - Dec. 17, US Trust, Leigh Bureau (Box E5)
      - Dec., AEA Christmas meeting (Box E5)
      - Dec., London, Italy, and Helsinki (Box E5)
    - 1986 (Box E6)
      - Refusals (Box E6)
    - 1987
      - Jan. 9, Faculty Club and Dr. Mariani (Box E6)
      - Jan. 15, Boston Association of Economists, data resources (Box E6)
      - Jan., George Pennacchi (Box E6)
      - Feb. 23, MIT alumni (Box E6)
      - March 12, Hamburger (Box E6)
      - March 13, IRS (Box E6)
      - March 16, LDC (Box E6)
      - March 16, Prodi (Box E6)
      - March 24, San Antonio, Texas (Box E6)
      - Apr. 9, Senior executives (Box E6)
      - Apr. 9, Sloan Club (Box E6)
      - Apr. 20, Michigan State University (Box E6)
      - Apr. 21, Kansas State University (Box E6)
      - Apr. 27, Venezuela NCR (Box E6)
      - May-June, Hicks lecture (Box E6)
      - June 17, TV contract for interview (Box E6)
      - Sept. 30, Fogg dinner NBER (Box E6)
      - Sept., Eliasson, Sweden: The European Recovery? (Box E6)
      - Sept., Italy, Spain (Box E6)
      - Oct. 15, Balanced budget amendment, Washington (Box E6)
      - Oct. 16, Competitiveness, Lincoln (Box E6)
      - Oct. 30, NY New School (Box E6)
      - Oct., Nynex (Box E6)
      - Nov. 2, Nomura Ritz (Box E6)
      - Nov. 4, EECM Debate (Box E6)
      - Nov. 12, Prodi luncheon, Skyroom Cambridge (Box E6)
      - Nov. 18, Italian visitors (Box E6)
      - Nov. 23-24, Washington National Conference (Box E6)
      - Fall, Kroeger visit (Box E6)
      - Dec. 4, Brandeis (Box E6)
      - Dec. 4, Endicott Sloan Fellows (Box E6)
      - Dec. 7, ILP visitor (Box E6)
      - Dec. 8, Visitors Rome/Bridge (Box E6)
      - Dec., Presidential task force (Box E6)
    - 1987 (Box E7)
      - Refusals, 3 folders (Box E7)
    - 1988
      - Feb. 23, Columbia NYC (Box E7)
      - Mar. 2-4, Philadelphia (Box E7)
      - Mar. 10, Eastern Economic Association (Box E7)
      - Apr. 11, Harvard (Box E7)
      - Apr., Italy prize (Box E7)
      - July 15, Vescovo (Box E7)
      - July, Aldo Enrici (Box E7)
      - Sept. 22, University of Hartford Honor Degree (Box E7)
      - Sept, Italy, France (Box E7)
      - Oct. 5, NBER (Box E7)
      - Oct. 14, Sonesta, NBER (Box E7)
      - Oct. 27, Mexico (Box E7)
      - Oct., International Media Productions (Box E7)
      - Nov. 2, De Paul University (Box E7)
      - Dec. 1, MFA University (Box E7)
      - Dec. 5, 92nd Street "Y," NYC (Box E7)
      - Dec. 8, RAI (Box E7)
      - Dec. 15, University of Florida Symposium (Box E7)
      - Dec. 22, Ralph Scally, Bank of Boston (Box E7)
      - Dec. 28, AEA, NYC (Box E7)
      - No month, Refusals, 2 folders (Box E7)
    - 1988-1991 and undated
      - Media (Box E7)
    - 1989
      - Jan. 10-11, Catholic University of Chile 100th anniversary (Box E7)
      - Jan. 15, Nihoh Computer conference (Box E7)
      - Feb. 23, Washington, DC (Box E7)
      - March 13, Taipei and Hongkong with Leah (Box E7)
      - March 29, SUNY Binghampton (Box E7)
      - Apr. 13, Oregon Nobel Symposium, Linfield College (Box E7)
      - May 5, NYSE academic seminar (Box E7)
      - May 22-23, FED and New School Honorary Degree (Box E7)
      - June 1-6, Italy and France (Box E7)
      - June 10, Michigan Honorary Degree (Box E7)
      - Sept. 14-15, Brookings "T" (Box E7)
      - Oct. 3, Lord/Erie, PA (Box E7)
      - Oct. 7, Banco Popular Pesarese (Box E7)
      - Oct. 9, Rotary Club, Florence (Box E7)
      - Oct. 14, Bergamo (Box E7)
      - Oct. 18, Roma (Box E7)
      - Oct. 21, Capri (Box E7)
      - Oct. 23, Naples (Box E7)
      - Oct. Bologna, Pesaro, Florence, Bergamo, Tuscany, Rome, Budapest (Box E7)
      - Nov. 14, Fletcher lecture (Box E7)
      - Nov. 15, Senate testimony (Box E7)
      - Nov. 30, Hartford (Box E7)
    - 1989 (Box E9)
      - Refusals, 2 folders (Box E9)
    - 1990
      - Jan. 8, Dreeze, Granada (Box E9)
      - Feb., Washington: Seidman Award (Box E9)
      - March 19, Windows on MIT (Box E9)
      - Apr. 5-6, Brookings (Box E9)
      - Apr. 24-27, Akron/St. Paul (Box E9)
      - May 3, Newark MIT Alam (Box E9)
      - May 4-5, NBER Washington (Box E9)
      - May 13, Urbana Honorary Degree (Box E9)
      - May 29, Bangkok (Box E9)
      - July 15, Edinburgh and Rome (Box E9)
      - Aug. 22, Barcelona, Parma, Venice (Box E9)
      - Sept. 13-14, Brookings (Box E9)
      - Oct. 11, Campus visit Hax (Box E9)
      - Oct. 26, NBER Cambridge (Box E9)
      - Nov. 9-10, Bard College, Lewy Trust (Box E9)
      - Nov. 16, BV lecture (Box E9)
      - Nov. 21, Carnegie (Box E9)
      - 1990 Refusals (Box E9)
    - 1991 (Box E10)
      - Jan. 13, Endicott Hoffman-La Roche (Box E10)
      - Jan., Ecuador (Box E10)
      - Feb. 14, Grinspan/Seidman IMF Wednesday Group, Washington (Box E10)
      - March 15, PBGH, PA; Eastern Economic Association (Box E10)
      - Apr. 11, Widener University, Philadelphia (Box E10)
      - Apr. 22, Telos conference, Milano (Box E10)
      - Apr.-May, Lisbon, Belgium, Rome, Sanremo (Box E10)
      - May 9-10, Vest events (Box E10)
      - May, China, Korea (Box E10)
      - June 27, Leverage Workouts Industry, N.Y. (Box E10)
      - July 19, Vineyard (Box E10)
      - Sept. 6, Baquerizo (Box E10)
      - Oct. 21-25, Amherst (Box E10)
      - Oct., Master's convocation (Box E10)
      - Nov., Franco's private consulting work in Italy (Box E10)
      - Dec. 4-11, Stockholm: Nobel (Box E10)
      - Sept. 12-13, Brookings, Washington (Box E10)
    - 1991 (Box E11)
      - Refusals (Box E11)
    - 1992
      - Jan., Banca d'Italia (Box E11)
      - Feb. 13, NAAS Breakfast (Box E11)
      - March 13, Fischer (Box E11)
      - Apr. 28-29, Mexico (Box E11)
      - Spring, Italy and Spain, Honorary Degree, Samuelson (Box E11)
      - July 11-13, Rome, Baldassarri, Mondragone (Box E11)
      - July 13-17, Singapore for Lee Kuan Yew, district visitor (Box E11)
      - July, PACAP Hongong, "Long-term Financing-Inflationary Environment" (Box E11)
      - 1992 Refusals (Box E11)
    - 1993
      - Apr. 1, Netherlands conference (Box E11)
      - June-July, Spain, Fininvest (Box E11)
      - June-July, Spain-Madrid, Bari, CISL, Escorial (Box E11)
      - July 12-16, Madrid-L'Escorial seminar (Box E11)
      - Sept. 6 - Oct., Spain: Jaime Prize in Economy (Box E11)
      - Sept. 13, Dr. Micossi (Confiindustria) (Box E11)
      - Sept. 13-14, Dr. Gebauer (Box E11)
      - Sept. 23- Oct. 8, Italy (Olivetti, Fiorella, Fininvest, Ceramica) (Box E11)
      - Oct.-Nov., Washington, NAFTA, Rudi (Box E11)
      - Dec. 8-18, Rome and Israel (Box E11)
      - 1993 Refusals (Box E11)
    - 1994 (Box E12)
      - Feb. 4, Reconstructing Italy conference (Box E12)
      - March 3, Gunzburg Center Harvard (Box E12)
      - Apr. 6, Washington conference, Italy after the Elections (Box E12)
      - Apr. 7-10, Venice, Acqua Vera (Box E12)
      - Apr., Frankfurt (Box E12)
      - Apr. 23-May 2, Frankfurt, London, Cambridge, Rome (Box E12)
      - May 9, Olivetti visit (Box E12)
      - July 8-11, China conference (Box E12)
      - July 15-16, Kouri conference (Box E12)
      - July 30, Rome-ISPE/CNR (Box E12)
      - July, Spain: summer course de Quinto (ICE/ABC), 2 folders (Box E12)
      - Sept. 19, Boston College conference (Box E12)
      - Oct. 7, Tinbergen lecture (Box E12)
      - Nov. 4-8, Italy (Box E12)
      - Nov. 17-18, MITSUI Group lunch (Box E12)
      - Nov. 28, Washington DC Trip: Nobel certificate (Box E12)
    - 1994 (Box E13)
      - Dec. 9, Behavioral Macroeconomics conference (Box E13)
      - Dec. 13, FISC/WISC meeting (Box E13)
      - Undated, Baseball card (Box E13)
      - 1994 Refusals (Box E13)
    - 1995
      - Jan., ASSA meeting (Box E13)
      - Mar. 27, Ezio Tarantelli commemoration (Box E13)
      - Mar. 29-Apr. 2, Bologna-Claremont (Box E13)
      - May-June, Italy (Olivetti) (Box E13)
      - June 8, Maggie Barreiro (Box E13)
      - June 14, La Terza Editore (Box E13)
      - June, Professorship of Financial Economics: chair announcement, 2 folders (Box E13)
      - Sept. 23, Chinese Finance Association (Box E13)
      - Oct. 17, Actuarial Enterprises (Box E13)
      - Dec. 1, European monetary conference (Box E13)
      - Undated, 5th Central Bank monetary conference (Box E13)
      - 1995 Refusals (Box E13)
    - 1996
      - Jan. 30-Feb. 5, Italy (Box E13)
      - Jan.-June and undated, Commitments (Box E13)
      - Apr. 18-20, Eastern Finance, Charlotte, NC (Box E13)
      - May 12-19, Italy (Box E13)
      - Sept. 11 - Oct. 9, Italy and Bilbao (Box E13)
      - Oct. 24-26, Jacksonville State University (Box E13)
      - Nov. 7, Baffi lecture (Box E13)
      - 1996 Refusals (Box E13)